# Le Thi Ngoc Hiep

MFDICAL REPRESENTATIVE

## **Objective**

Short term goal: becoming a high-quality medical representative, achieving assigned sales, improving my communication skill, building good relationships and flexibly solving problems. Long term goal: in 3-5 years, sale manager help me assess my potential and direct me become a sale manager or develop in marketing position.



## Education -

### HO CHI MINH UNIVERSITY OF MEDICINE AND PHARMACY

**SEP 2012 - JULY 2017** 

Major: Pharmacy

GPA: 7.73



# **Work Experience**

PRIVATE TUTOR OCT 2016 - PRESENT

Teaching Math and Physic in English for student of SNA (School of North America)

Main responsibilities:

- -Reading the textbooks and give lesson in the easiest way for student to understand. Gain:
- -Improving English skill in: Comprehensive reading, speaking and writing
- -Effective time magagement skills

# A

## **Activities**

# A REVIEW COURSE OF DEMARTOGLYPHIC IN CAD (CENTER FOR MAY 2018 - JUNE 2018 APPLIED DEMARTOGLYPHICS)

- Having an overview about demartoglyphics
- Understanding myself as well as finding the right way to learn and work.
- Recognizing someone's character bases on demartoglyphics

### TRADITIONAL CAMPING AT UNIVERSITY

**JAN 2016 - MAR 2016** 

Member of musical comedy (2016) and aerobic group (2013)

- Improving team spirit
- Managing individual schedule and understanding that every single member's work effect the whole process of group

#### WHITE BLOUSE VOLUNTEER

OCT 2015 - 2016

- Giving direction in the University medical center HCMC
- Joining some extra- activities in hospital an impoving comunated skill

# **Certifications & Awards**

Korean certificate, Basic 2 2016

Daewoong Foundation 2016



- m Oct 7th, 1994
- Female
- 01653888117
- lethingochiep7894@gmail.co m
- Tam Danh st., Ward 4, Dict 8, CHMC

## SKILLS

Enthusiasm to learn

English skill

**Public Speaking** 

IT skill

## INTERESTS

- Reading
- Music
- Doing yoga